(Alfred:)I'll go with you.
(Leonard:)That still leaves me
here with him.
Hang on, hang on!
We're smart, we can
figure this out.
Okay, so: Mary and Beverly
can't be together.
Uh, Alfred and Beverly
Leonard and I can't be together.
Now, I could be with Alfred...
but I don't like his face.
Oh, here! I've got it!
(Amy:)Who's ready for a wedding?
(Sheldon:)Great, now I have
to start all over.
(Wyatt:)So how's the world
of pharmaceuticals treating you?
(Penny:)Pretty good. I actually
just got assigned
(Penny:)a much better territory.
(Susan:)See what happens
when you work hard?
(Randall:)Hey, she just sells drugs.
I had to make 'em.
(Susan:)Okay, that's enough.
(Susan:)No more drug talk
for the rest of this trip.
(Wyatt:)I'll drink to that.
(Susan:)Haven't you had enough?
(Wyatt:)Penny drinks
more than I do.
(Penny:)Well, I learned
from the best.
Aw!